Register of the Socialist Workers Party Records, 1928-2002
Wisconsin Historical Society
- Part 2 (Micro 2086): Additions, 1994-2000, Micro 2086; 24 reels of microfilm (35 mm)
  - 1999, Correspondence, Branch Circulars, and Discussion Bulletins not received.
    - PB/PC/NC Minutes
      - January-March (Reel 16, Frame 1)
      - April-July (Reel 17, Frame 1)
      - August-September (Reel 18, Frame 1)
      - November-December (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Information Bulletins (Reel 19, Frame 607)
  - 2000, Correspondence, Branch Circulars, and Discussion Bulletins not received.
    - PB/PC/NC Minutes
      - January-March (Reel 20, Frame 1)
      - April-June (Reel 21, Frame 1)
      - July-August (Reel 22, Frame 1)
      - September-October (Reel 23, Frame 1)
      - November-December (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Information Bulletins (Reel 24, Frame 528)
- Part 3 (M74-109): Additions, undated, M74-109; 2 tape recordings
  Speech on feminism and socialism by Linda Jenness.
- Part 4 (M81-206): Additions, 1967-1972, M81-206; 34 photographs
  Photographs from The Militant files; primarily of anti-Vietnam War demonstrations (in New York City, Washington, D.C., Los Angeles, Detroit, Cleveland, Madison, Wisconsin, Berkeley, California, Ann Arbor, and Riverside, California), 1967-1972. Also included is a 1966 photograph of the Fort Hood 3, one of Resurrection City in 1968, a Lowndes County resident at a civil rights demonstration in Mississippi, and three images from demonstrations in Chicago during the 1968 Democratic Convention.
- Part 5 (M85-006): Additions, 1928-2001, M85-006; 140 c.f. (138 record center cartons and 5 archives boxes)
  Files documenting the lawsuit Socialist Workers Party v. United States Attorney General, an action brought by the Socialist Workers Party (SWP), its youth arm, the Young Socialist Alliance (YSA), and certain members of the SWP against the United States of America and certain officials of the United States. The SWP, et al. contended that they had been improperly viewed by various Government agencies as threats to national security, and had been subjected to infiltration, disruption and harassment in violation of their legal rights. The action was commenced on July 18, 1973, and was finally decided in 1986. Materials in this accession relate to the ongoing case and include the Socialist Workers Party internal questionnaires regarding FBI harassment, FBI documents obtained through FOIA, COINTELPRO documents, military intelligence documents, CIA files, plaintiff's exhibits and evidence, and case briefs, subpoenas, motions, court orders, depositions and witness testimony.
  - Questionnaires Answered by Socialist Workers Party (SWP) and Young Socialists of America (YSA) Members, 1975, These files contain information collected by the SWP regarding instances of FBI harassment. Box 74 contains questionnaire indices by date, location and incident.
    - Aber, Joel -- Dawson, Kip (Box 1)
    - DeBerry, Clifton -- Hyink, Larry (Box 2)
    - Indecipherable -- Murphey, James (Box 3)
    - Murphy, Fred -- Sell, Evelyn (Box 4)
    - Semerad, Marty -- Zon, Marie Gislaine (Box 5)
  - FBI Documents Covering Wiretaps, Bugs, and Break-Ins of SWP, pre-1960, Summary of these documents is in box 76.
    - 1945-1953 (Control Number 1-16) (Box 6)
    - 1946-1949 (Control Number 17-19) (Box 7)
    - 1945-1948, 1951-1952 (Control Number 30-50) (Box 8)
    - 1945-1949 (Control Number 51-59) (Box 9)
    - 1945-1948 (Control Number 60-70) (Box 10)
    - 1947-1949 (Control Number 71-88) (Box 11)
    - 1945, 1948-1949, 1952, 1954 (Control Number 89-105) (Box 12)
    - 1947, 1952-1953, 1958-1959 (Control Number 106-114) (Box 13)
    - 1948-1950, 1957, 1959, 1963 (Control Number 115-123) (Box 14)
    - 1945-1948, 1950-1956 (Control Number 124-134) (Box 15)
    - 1949, 1954-1958 (Control Number 135-161) (Box 16)
    - 1943, 1947, 1949, 1950-1951, 1957, 1959 (Control Number 162-182) (Box 17)
    - 1946-1949, 1951, 1954, 1959 (Control Number 183-214) (Box 18)
    - 1943, 1945, 1946, 1948-1951, 1957-1958 (Control Number 214-225) (Box 19)
  - Informer Files, Informant reports detail information given by FBI informants about Socialist Workers Party meetings, members and activities. Administrative volumes contain administrative paperwork pertaining to the hiring, payment and placement of informers.
    - George Davis (number 220)
      - Informant reports, volumes 1-14 (Box 19)
      - Informant reports, volumes 15-23 (Box 20)
      - Informant reports, volumes 24-38 (Box 21)
      - Informant reports, volumes 37-40 (Box 22)
    - Orrie Norton (number 2254)
      - Informant reports, volumes 1-6 (Box 22)
      - Informant reports, volumes 7-14 (Box 23)
      - Informant reports, volumes 15-16 (Box 24)
      - Administrative, volumes 1-5 (Box 24)
    - Stephen Cooper (number 3931), administrative volume 1, informant reports, volumes 1-4 (Box 24)
    - John Neal (number 602), administrative volumes 1-2, informant report, volume 1 (Box 25)
    - Robert Laczi (number 1123), administrative volume 1, informant reports, volumes 1-2 (Box 25)
    - Rodney Hertz (number 1873), administrative volume 1, informant reports, volumes 1-6 (Box 25)
    - Ralph Desimone (number 4358), administrative volumes 1-3, informant reports, volumes 1-4 (Box 26)
    - August Namors (number 6)
      - Informant reports, volumes 1-18 (Box 26)
      - Informant reports, volumes 19-32 (Box 27)
      - Informant reports, volumes 33-42 (Box 28)
    - Nicolas Abbruzzese (number 694)
      - Informant reports, volumes 1-2 (Box 28)
      - Informant report, volume 3 (Box 29)
    - Arthur Bryne (number 2906), administrative volume 1, informant reports, volumes 1-3 (Box 29)
    - John Hollowell (number 1046)
      - Administrative volumes 1-3, informant reports, volumes 1-5 (Box 29)
      - Informant reports, volumes 6-18 (Box 30)
      - Informant reports, volumes 19-31 (Box 31)
      - Informant reports, volumes 32-43 (Box 32)
    - Anthony Bachman (number 1321)
      - Informant reports, volumes 1-15 (Box 32)
      - Informant reports, volumes 16-20, 39-48 (Box 33)
      - Informant reports, volumes 49-65 (Box 34)
      - Informant reports, volumes 66-77 (Box 35)
      - Informant reports, volumes 78-81 (Box 36)
    - Edward Heisler (number 7027)
      - Informant reports, volumes 1-4, 6-7, 9 (Box 36)
      - Informant reports, volumes 10-11, 15, 20-21, 25-30 (Box 37)
      - Informant reports, volumes 31-32, 34-40 (Box 38)
  - Kelly Memo Documents, 1960-1975, The Kelly memo is a 1957 communication from FBI supervisor J.G. Kelly to the FBI field office in Atlanta, Georgia, warning about possible communist infiltration into the Civil Rights movement. The documents in this series relate to FBI counterintelligence activities and are summarized in an index in box 76.
    - Documents 1-000 - 1-080 (Box 38)
    - Documents 1-081 -1-154 (Box 39)
    - Documents 1-2322 - 1-3391 (Box 40)
    - Documents 1-3416 --1-4272 (Box 41)
    - Documents 1-4273 --1-5358 (Box 42)
    - Documents 1-5359- 1-6263 (Box 43)
    - Documents 1-6264 - 1-7520 (Box 44)
    - Documents 1-7521 - 1-9349 (Box 45)
    - Documents 1-9350 - 1-10416 (Box 46)
    - Documents 1-10417 - 1-11299 (Box 47)
    - Documents 1-11300 - 1-11933 (Box 48)
    - Documents 1-11934 - 1-12599 (Box 49)
    - Documents 1-12600 - 1-14388 (Box 50)
    - 1942 memo on Socialist Workers Party, document 1-14287 (Box 50)
    - Assorted key policy documents 1-13841 - 1-14288 (Box 50)
    - Allan Selling documents 1-13846 - 1-13856 (Box 50)
    - Breitman documents 1-11263 - 1-11278 (Box 50)
    - FBI documents 1-14289 - 1-14295 (Box 50)
    - Mail cover documents 1-12927 - 1-12995 (Box 50)
    - Milwaukee burglary documents 1-12772 - 1-12926 (Box 50)
    - Waters documents 1-112895 - 1-12902 (Box 50)
  - FBI Investigative Files, FOIA Files, and COINTELPRO Files, 1947-1973, Numbered documents beginning with S are part of the S Series and are indexed in the Summary of S Series binder in box 76.
    - FBI investigative files
      - Documents S1-S16 (Box 50)
      - Documents S16-S104 (Box 51)
    - Socialist Workers Party COINTELPRO documents S114-S404 (Box 51)
    - New Left COINTELPRO documents S418-S516 (Box 51)
    - Peter Camejo investigation
      - Documents S620-S628 (Box 51)
      - Document S629 (Box 52)
      - Documents produced 6/28/1977, 6/12/1978, 8/1/1978, undated (Box 52)
    - Fred Halstead FBI documents S631, A-D, and CIA files (Box 52)
    - Socialist Workers Party Internal Security
      - Documents S820-S849 (Box 52)
      - Documents S850-S1044, 12 folders (Box 53)
      - Documents S1045-S1206, 10 folders (Box 54)
    - Socialist Workers Party and Young Socialist Alliance Internal Security
      - Documents S1207-S1299 (Box 54)
      - Documents S1300-S1449, 9 folders (Box 55)
      - Documents S1450-S1610, 11 folders (Box 56)
      - Documents S1611-S1769, 10 folders (Box 57)
      - Documents S1771-S1831 (Box 58)
    - Internal Revenue Service documents 2016-2568 (Box 59)
    - Internal Revenue Service documents produced 07/1976 (Box 59)
    - Army documents produced 04/1976 (Box 59)
    - Army documents 5145-5192 (Wattenmaker file) (Box 59)
    - Army Security Board
      - Sydney Stapleton 5304 (Box 59)
      - Peter Camejo 5305 (Box 59)
      - Fred Halstead 5306 (Box 59)
      - John C. Hawkins 5307 (Box 59)
      - Edward Heisler 5308 (Box 59)
      - Larry Seigle 5311 (Box 59)
      - Young Socialist Alliance and Student Mobilization Committee (Box 59)
      - Documents 5318-7761 (Box 59)
    - Navy documents produced 06/1976 (Box 59)
    - CIA files on the 35, documents 7242-7492 (Box 60)
    - CIA case files
      - Documents 7493-7758 (Box 60)
    - CIA Office of Security files (Box 60)
    - CIA Operation Chaos (Box 61)
    - Defense Department Philadelphia documents (Box 61)
    - Thorstad FBI file (Box 61)
    - Department of Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms documents (Box 61)
    - Department of Justice documents (Box 61)
    - Miscellaneous Military Information documents (Box 61)
    - Hampton Civil Suit (Box 61)
    - FBI files
      - Fred Halstead, E-G (Box 62)
      - Fred Halstead Vietnam trip (Box 62)
      - Morris Starksy (Box 62)
      - Jack Barnes (Box 62)
      - Jack Barnes CIA file (Box 62)
      - Young Socialist Alliance (Box 62)
      - Jim Miller (Box 62)
      - James Boulton (Box 62)
      - National Student Coalition Against Racism (Box 62)
      - Dan Fein (Box 62)
      - Farrell Dobbs (Box 62)
      - Jim Watson (Box 62)
      - Seattle Socialist Workers Party (Box 62)
      - James Kutchner (Box 62)
      - Derek Jeffers (Box 62)
      - Laura Carnes (Box 62)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 62)
    - FBI COINTELPRO, documents S1841-S2046 (Box 63)
    - Communist Party COINTELPRO, documents S571-S619 (Box 63)
    - New Left COINTELPRO, S2047-S2118 (Box 63)
    - Socialist Workers Party and Communist Party COINTELPRO, Documents S2119-S2180 (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous COINTELPRO, documents S2182-S2255 (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous COINTELPRO (Box 63)
    - Burglary documents S632-S819 (Box 63)
    - FBI investigative files, S530-S570 (Box 63)
    - FBI investigative files, S621-S625 (Box 63)
    - FBI Socialist Workers Party disruption program, documents released 12/1/1978 (Box 63)
    - FBI Socialist Workers Party disruption program, 1-682 (Box 63)
    - Socialist Workers Party National Convention, Oberlin, Ohio (Box 63)
    - Socialist Workers Party-New York Local, 1-354 (Box 63)
    - Socialist Workers Party Internal Security and COINTELPRO (Box 63)
    - Arlene Slaughter FBI file (Box 64)
    - Women's Liberation Movement FBI file, documents 1-1322 (Box 64)
    - Immigration Naturalization Service
      - Documents 1-1332 (Box 64)
      - Documents 1333-1797 (Box 65)
    - Immigration Naturalization Service file 850.400 (Box 65)
    - Secret Service file, documents 9003-9206 (Box 65)
    - FBI Socialist Workers Party files, documents 12996-13740 (Box 65)
    - Navy Yard Documents (Box 65)
    - Statement of Alan Jerome Kohlman, page 1-849 (Box 65)
    - Chicago Socialist Workers Party (Box 65)
    - Open letter replies regarding Legion of Justice (Box 65)
    - Legion of Justice (Box 65)
    - Legion of Justice Chicago (Box 65)
    - Committee for Defense Against Terrorist Attacks (DATA), 1971 (Box 65)
    - DATA and Legion of Justice (Box 65)
    - Chicago-DeKalb (Box 65)
    - Sample Labor Resolutions (Box 65)
    - Edward Heisler (interrogatories summary in box 93)
      - Informant reports, volumes 5, 8, 12, 13, 14, 16-19, 22-24, 31, 33 (Box 66)
      - Selective Service files (Box 66)
      - Correspondence regarding Edward Heisler documents (Box 66)
      - Deletions (Box 66)
      - FOIA documents (Box 66)
      - Exposure as informant (Box 66)
      - FBI security matter (Box 66)
      - Chicago informant reports, volumes 1-5 (Box 66)
      - Chicago informant reports, volumes 6-20 (Box 67)
    - Shannon Measaw
      - FBI file (Box 67)
      - Informant reports, volumes 1-8 (Box 67)
    - James Nilson informant file, volume 1 (Box 67)
    - Pre-1960 FBI cover sheets (Box 67)
    - New Orleans Red Squad (Box 67)
    - FBI file Muslim Mosque, Inc. (Box 67)
    - CIA file Muslim Mosque, Inc. (Box 67)
    - Abdeen Jabara FBI file (Box 67)
    - Carl Stern COINTELPRO (Box 67)
    - Kenyatta COINTELPRO (Box 67)
    - Black Nationalist COINTELPRO (Box 67)
    - Operation Hoodwink (Box 67)
    - Klu Klux Klan COINTELPRO (Box 67)
    - FBI file Malcolm Little (Box 67)
    - FBI file Malcolm Little (continued) (Box 68)
    - FBI file Muslim Mosque, Inc. (Box 68)
    - FBI documents
      - Numbers 10-36 (Box 68)
      - Numbers 43-103 (Box 68)
      - Numbers 514-611 (Box 68)
      - Numbers 1008-12954 (Box 68)
    - James Boulton file (Box 68)
    - Timothy Redfearn (summary information of these documents can be found in box 76)
      - Documents 1-199 (Box 68)
      - Documents 200-1921 (Box 69)
      - Related material (Box 69)
      - Materials to John Adams (Box 69)
    - Detroit Red Squad (Box 69)
    - COINTELPRO summaries, documents 1-5, 7, 10-15, 18-22, 24, 26-29 (Box 69)
    - Detroit Red Squad, documents 1 - 1506 (Box 70)
    - Detroit Socialist Workers Party materials (Box 70)
    - Detroit Waivers (Box 70)
    - Money Paid to Member Informers (Box 70)
    - Informers' Interrogatories
      - Numbers 1000 - 1166 (Box 70)
      - Numbers 1167 - 1609, 14 folders (Box 71)
      - Numbers 1610 - 2119, 13 folders (Box 72)
      - Numbers 2120 - 2315 (Box 73)
    - Questionnaires (in boxes 1-5) index by date, location and incident (Box 74)
    - Edward Heisler Army files (Box 75)
    - Edward Heisler CIA files (Box 75)
    - Edward Heisler Red Squad (Box 75)
    - Jose Gutierrez CIA file (Box 75)
    - Agent John Almon (Box 75)
    - Winter-Pike Report (summary of evidence up until January 1980) (Box 76)
    - Summary of pre-1960 wiretap documents (in boxes 6-19) (Box 76)
    - Summary of pre-1960 wiretap documents (in boxes 6-19) (Box 116)
    - Summary of Kelly Memo documents (in boxes 39-50) (Box 76)
    - Summary of S Series FBI documents (in boxes 50-58) (Box 76)
    - Summary of Redfearn files (in boxes 68-69) (Box 76)
  - Plaintiff's Production Pre-Trial Plan
    - Documents to be submitted as evidence, part I - part II, section B, volume 4 (Box 77)
    - Documents to be submitted as evidence, part II, section C - part II, section F volume 2 (Box 78)
    - John O'Brien deposition (Box 78)
  - Plaintiff's Evidence
    - Plaintiff's exhibit I, volumes 1-2, Nature of Organization, Goals and Activities (Box 79)
    - Plaintiff's exhibit II
      - Section A, volumes 1-2, FBI burglaries (Box 79)
      - Section B
        - Volumes 1-6, FBI intrusions into private correspondence (Box 79)
        - Volumes 7-16 (Box 80)
        - Volumes 17-23 (Box 81)
        - Volumes 1-2, Informer burglaries (Box 81)
        - Volume 1, COINTELPRO and disruption activities (Box 81)
      - Section D
        - Volume 2 (Box 82)
        - Subsection 1, Disruption of Socialist Workers Party Election Campaigns (Box 82)
      - Section E, Informer activity (Box 82)
      - Section F
        - Subsection 1, volumes 1-3, Direct electronic surveillance (Box 82)
        - Subsection 2, volume 1, Incidental electronic surveillance (Box 82)
        - Volumes 1-2, Electronic surveillance James Cannon microphone logs (Box 82)
        - Volumes 3-4 (Box 83)
      - Section G
        - Volumes 1-4, 7-15, Right-wing groups (Box 83)
        - Subsection 5, volumes 1-2, O'Brien deposition (Box 83)
      - Section H, volumes 1-2, Interference with employment (Box 83)
      - Section I
        - Subsection 1, Selective enforcement of the law- INS/FBI program to deport Socialist Workers Party members (Box 83)
        - Subsection 2, Selective enforcement of the law-IRS (Box 83)
        - Subsection 3, Selective enforcement of the law-miscellaneous (Box 83)
      - Section J, Mail and trash cover (Box 83)
      - Section K, CIA (Box 83)
      - Section L, Army (Box 83)
      - Section M, volumes 1-2, Blacklisting (Box 84)
    - Plaintiff's exhibit IV
      - Section A (Box 84)
      - Section B, volumes 1-7 (Box 84)
    - Plaintiff's exhibit V, volumes 1-4, Deposition transcripts (Box 85)
    - Plaintiff's exhibit VI, volumes 1-4, FOIA documents regarding Farrell Dobbs and Jack Barnes (Box 85)
    - Plaintiff's exhibit VII
      - Volumes 1-4 Army, Air Force and Navy documents (Box 85)
      - Volumes 5-9 (Box 86)
    - Plaintiff's exhibit VIII
      - Volumes 1-6, Stolen documents (Box 86)
      - Volumes 7-16 (Box 87)
      - Volumes 17-19 (Box 88)
    - Plaintiff's exhibit IX
      - Volumes 1-5, Stolen documents (Box 88)
      - Volumes 6-10 (Box 89)
    - Plaintiff's exhibit X, Federal Tort Claims and Evelyn Sell (Box 89)
    - Plaintiff's evidence, 267-269 (Box 89)
    - Plaintiff's evidence, 270-274 (Box 90)
    - 1971 FI (Box 90)
    - 1972 FI (Box 90)
    - 1973 FI (Box 90)
    - 1974 FI (Box 90)
    - 1975 FI (Box 90)
    - International Control Commission (Box 90)
    - Plaintiff's evidence, documents 14390-15254 (Box 91)
    - Plaintiff's evidence II
      - Section G (Box 91)
      - Section H (Box 91)
      - Section I, volumes 1-3 (Box 91)
      - Section J (Box 91)
      - Section K (Box 91)
      - Section L (Box 91)
      - Section M (Box 91)
    - Plaintiff's evidence III (Box 91)
    - Depositions
      - Nancy Cole (Box 91)
      - Caroline Sheppard (Box 91)
      - David Prince (Box 91)
      - Margaret Brady (Box 92)
      - Anthony Thomas (Box 92)
      - Morris Starsky (Box 92)
      - Peter Camejo (Box 92)
      - Willie Mae Reid (Box 92)
      - Jack Barnes (Box 92)
      - Timothy Wohlforth (Box 92)
      - Andrew Pulley (Box 92)
      - Richard Feignberg (Box 92)
      - Mary-Alice Waters (Box 92)
      - Gershon Horowitz (Box 92)
      - Robert Schwarz (Box 92)
      - Linda Jenness (Box 93)
    - Edward Heisler interrogatories summary (documents in box 66) (Box 93)
    - Box documents (Box 93)
    - FBI procedures (Box 93)
    - FBI informer privilege (Box 93)
    - FBI director to Philadelphia communications (Box 93)
    - Internal Revue Service documents (Box 93)
    - John Hollowell informant report 58 (Box 93)
    - Timothy Redfearn burglary of Denver Socialist Workers Party headquarters (Box 93)
    - Legion of Justice documents (Box 93)
    - CIA guidelines (Box 93)
    - Rodney Hertz informer file (Box 93)
    - ELSUR, document 017984 (Box 93)
    - Plaintiff's exhibit, 276 and 687 (Box 93)
    - Grand Jury material, 1976 (Box 93)
    - Minutes of Socialist Workers Party Political Committee (Box 93)
    - Internationalist Tendency material (Box 93)
    - Young Socialist Alliance National Conventions, 1967-1974 (Box 93)
    - Plenum of Young Socialist Alliance National Committee (Box 93)
    - Socialist Workers Party National Conventions Minutes (Box 93)
    - Secret Service documents produced 4/28/1977 (Box 93)
    - Break through FBI files (Box 93)
    - COINTELPRO, Stern and Starsky (Box 93)
    - COINTELPRO initiation and termination (Box 93)
    - CIA Office of Security documents (Box 93)
    - Internal Revenue Service documents (Box 93)
    - Wattenmaker originals (Box 93)
    - Fred Halstead CIA, FBI, FOIA files (Box 93)
    - COINTELPRO memo (Box 93)
    - 19th informer file (Box 93)
    - Plaintiff's document production 4th set (Box 94)
    - Material on Fourth International and Internationalist Tendency (Box 94)
    - Evidence of receipt of stolen property (Box 94)
    - Peter Camejo vs. Department of Justice (Box 94)
    - Secret Service Young Socialist Alliance convention file (Box 94)
    - CIA Project 2 (Box 94)
    - Ralph Desimone file (Box 95)
    - V. Starr (Box 94)
    - Responses to interrogatories (Box 94)
    - Farrell Dobbs documents (Box 94)
    - FOIA documents
      - Seattle branch (Box 94)
      - Fred Halstead (Box 94)
      - Farrell Dobbs (Box 94)
      - Jack Barnes (Box 94)
      - Joseph Hansen (Box 94)
      - Gary Balsam (Box 95)
      - Edward Heisler (Box 95)
    - Kelly Memo documents (Box 95)
    - FBI factual research (Box 95)
    - Third supplementary response to requests for production of documents of the FBI director (Box 95)
    - Plaintiff's production to the defense, undated (Box 95)
    - Plaintiff's production to the defense, Young Socialist Alliance financial information (Box 95)
    - Originals of Young Socialist Alliance materials, produced 1/13/1981 (Box 96)
    - Plaintiff's production to the defense
      - Socialist Workers Party financial information (Box 96)
      - Produced 3/12/1981-6/24/1981 (Box 96)
    - Defendant's production to the plaintiff
      - Office of Security documents (Box 96)
      - Army documents (Box 97)
      - Internal Revenue Service (Box 97)
      - Navy documents (Box 97)
    - Prince production (Box 97)
    - Defendant's production to the plaintiff
      - CIA Operation Chaos (Box 98)
      - CIA List of 35 (Box 98)
      - CIA Camejo FOIA (Box 98)
      - CIA/FBI documents (Box 98)
      - Fred Halstead CIA documents (Box 98)
      - Morris Starsky CIA documents (Box 98)
    - Defendant's trial exhibits
      - AA-FZ (Box 98)
      - GA-KZ (Box 99)
      - LA-OE (Box 99)
      - A-Z (Box 99)
      - OE-TZ (Box 100)
    - Defendant's exhibits not introduced as evidence (Box 100)
    - Index to trial record and witness list (Box 100)
    - Plaintiff's trial exhibits in evidence
      - Numbers 1-125 (Box 100)
      - Numbers 126-525 (Box 101)
      - Numbers 526-798 (Box 102)
    - Plaintiff's evidence II, section B
      - Volumes 1-3, FBI intrusion into private correspondence and documents (Box 102)
      - Volumes 4-13 (Box 103)
      - Volumes 14-23 (Box 104)
    - Plaintiff's evidence VIII
      - Volume 1, Stolen documents (Box 104)
      - Volumes 2-12 (Box 105)
      - Volumes 13-19 (Box 106)
    - Plaintiff's evidence IX, volumes 1-3, Stolen documents (Box 106)
    - Plaintiff's evidence IV, volumes 3-10 (Box 107)
    - Plaintiff's trial exhibits, numbers 178-180 (Box 108)
    - Defendant's post trial brief, section VI-VIII, X (Box 108)
    - Plaintiff's discovery productions to the defendant, Fourth International (Box 108)
    - Federal Election Commission report for Socialist Workers Party National Campaign Committee (Box 109)
    - Plaintiff's post trial brief appendices A, C, D, E, F, H (Box 109)
    - Index of Defendant's post trial submissions (Box 109)
    - Defendant's post trial briefs I-IV (Box 109)
    - Plaintiff's memo on attorney fees (Box 109)
    - Plaintiff's attorney fees exhibit A-D (Box 109)
    - Plaintiff's Federal Tort Claims Act forms (Box 109)
    - Plaintiff's discovery production to the defendant
      - Fourth International (Box 110)
      - Internationalist Tendency (Box 110)
      - Financial records (Box 110)
      - Produced 2/6/1975 (Box 110)